{
    "subject": "resource/Battle_of_the_Network_Stars",
    "predicate": "ontology/numberOfEpisodes",
    "object": "19",
    "human_readable": "The Battle of the Network Stars has 19 episodes.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.699522852897644,
            "question": "How many episodes does The Battle of the Network Stars have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.67001873254776,
            "question": "What network aired The Battle of the Network Stars?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6140524744987488,
            "question": "What is the name of the show with 19 episodes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.559197723865509,
            "question": "What type of show is The Battle of the Network Stars?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5569776892662048,
            "question": "Who are some of the participants in The Battle of the Network Stars?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5207574367523193,
            "question": "Was The Battle of the Network Stars a successful show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4860875904560089,
            "question": "Could you tell me more about The Battle of the Network Stars?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40524980425834656,
            "question": "When did The Battle of the Network Stars air?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38262882828712463,
            "question": "Are there any spin-offs or related shows to The Battle of the Network Stars?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23914124071598053,
            "question": "Is there a specific number of episodes for this TV show?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Battle of the Network Stars has 19 episodes.",
            "html": "dbpedia_823_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any spin-offs or related shows to The Battle of the Network Stars?",
            "html": "dbpedia_823_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did The Battle of the Network Stars air?",
            "html": "dbpedia_823_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you tell me more about The Battle of the Network Stars?",
            "html": "dbpedia_823_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_823_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_823_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_823_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_823_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_823_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_823_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_823_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_823_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_823_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_823_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents indeed mention \"Battle of the Network Stars\" and state that there were a total of 19 competitions held, all aired by ABC. This confirms the triple statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents repeatedly mention that there were a total of nineteen competitions or episodes of \"Battle of the Network Stars,\" confirming the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}